Guide to the Rice University Past Faculty and Staff records, 1961-1996 UA 008
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Past Faculty and Staff A-Z, 1915-2003, 119315
  - Meguid, A. R. Abdul - Economics (offer not accepted), 1963-1964; 168810 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Meier, Kenneth J. - Political Science, 1975-1979 [?]; 168811 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Melitz, Jack - Economics, 1962-1964; 168812 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Mellers, Wilfrid - Head of Shepherd School of Music (offer not accepted), 1970; 168813 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Melton, CAPT Wade I. - Naval Science, 1979-1981 [?]; 168814 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Merer, Anthony John - Chemistry, 1982; 168815 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Meyer, Robert Kenneth - Philosophy, 1966; 168816 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Meyerhoff, Henry J. - Electrical Engineering, 1966; 168817 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Meyerowitz, Joseph H. - Psychology, 1966; 168818 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Miller, Charles Keith - Mathematics, 1963-1964; 168819 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Miller, Dennis R. - Shepherd School of Music, 1980-1981; 168820 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Miller, Michael Barry - History, 1977-1980; 168821 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Milligan, Winfred O. - Chemistry, 1933-1963; 168822 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Milovanovic, Jovan - Chemistry, 1977; 168823 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Milton, George Cohle - Health and Physical Education, 1962-1963; 168824 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Minear, John W. - Geology, 1981; 168825 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Minnick, Robert C. - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, 1971-1972; 168826 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Minter, David L. - English, 1967-1980; 168827 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Mirman, Leonard J. - Economics, 1982; 168828 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Mitchell, Earl Douglas - German, 1960-1961; 168829 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Mitchell, O. Jack - Architecture, 1966-1992; 168830 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Moake, Joel L. - Biomedical Engineering, 1975-1980; 168831 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Modrak, Deborah - Philosophy, 1974-1982; 168832 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Montgomery, Stephen N. - Real Estate Development, n.d.; 168833 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Monts, James Kenneth - Sociology, 1972-1976; 168834 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Mooney, James William - History, 1977-1979; 168835 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Moraud, Marcel - French, 1925-1956; 168836 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Morgan, Frank - Mathematics, 1982-1983; 168837 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Morgan, Mark A. - Political Science, 1983-1984; 168838 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Morimoto, Akihiro - Mathematics, 1965-1966; 168839 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Morrison, Lt. JG Richard N. - Naval Science (photograph), 1973; 168840 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Morrow, Carolyn R. - Spanish, 1966-1968; 168841 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Morrow, James Allen - Mathematics, 1973; 168842 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Morse, Michael D. - Chemistry, 1981-1983; 168843 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Moser, Charles F. - President of Development, 1970-1974; 168844 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Mueller, Ernst-August - Linguistics and Semiotics, 1983-1984; 168845 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Mukamel, Shaul - Chemistry, 1978-1981; 168846 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Muñoz, Olivia - Spanish, 1965-1968; 168847 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Murphy, Kevin R. - Psychology, 1979-1981; 168848 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Mutchler, Gordon S. - Physics, 1973-1974; 168849 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Myers, Robert L. - French and Spanish, 1952-1963 [?]; 168850 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Nachshon, Yehuda - Electrical Engineering, 1982-1983; 168851 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Naman, Israel Adrian - Architecture, 1973-1980; 168852 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Natelson, Ethan A. - Biomedical Engineering, 1975-1979; 168853 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Neale, Walter Castle - Economics, 1963; 168854 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Neidinger, William J. - History, 1977-1981; 168855 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Nelson, CAPT Eric A. - Naval Science, 1977-1978; 168856 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Nelson, Raymond A. - Health and Physical Education, 1962-1963; 168857 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Nelson, William H. - History, 1954-1963; 168858 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Ness, Norman T. - Economics, 1961-1966; 168859 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Nettleton, Lewis L. - Geology, 1966, 1971-1976; 168860 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Newcomb, Horace M. - Sociology, 1984; 168861 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Newell, Henry - Philosophy, 1982-1983; 168862 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Newman, M. H. A. - Mathematics, 1966; 168863 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Newpost, John P. - Religious Studies, 1971-1973, 1976-1979; 168864 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Nichols, James R. - French, 1971-1975; 168865 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Nogee, Joseph Lippman - Political Science, 1982; 168866 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Norbeck, Edward - Anthropology and Sociology, 1961-1981; 168867 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Nordgren, Ronald P. - Mechanical Engineering, 1965-1968; 168868 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Norman, John Duncan - Environmental Science, 1964-1966; 168869 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Norman, MAJ Phil R. - Military Science, 1969-1973; 168870 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - North, Douglass C. - Political Economy, 1979; 168871 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Nudelman, Harvey B. - Biology/Electrical Engineering, 1972-1979; 168872 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Nunn, Addison Stayton - Architecture, 1928-1945, 1961; 168873 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Nunnally, Jum C. - Psychology, 1979; 168874 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Nydegger, Rudy V. - Psychology, 1970-1977; 168875 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Obear, Frederick W. - Visiting Academic Administrator, 1967-1968; 168877 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Ogle, Philip Brandon - Fine Arts, 1975-1976; 168878 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - O'Grady, Gerald - English, 1962-1967; 168879 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - O'Keefe, Richard L. - Librarian, 1962 [?] -1979; 168880 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Oliver, Covey T. - Jones School of Administration, 1978-1981; 168881 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Oliver, Harold H. - Religious Studies, 1980-1981; 168882 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Olson, John David - Biomedical Engineering, 1980-1982; 168883 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - O'Neill, Michael W. - Civil Engineering, 1975; 168884 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Oran, Cenap - Civil Engineering, 1964-1967; 168885 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Oshima, Sueo - Religious Studies, 1971-1979 [?]; 168886 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Outler, Albert - Philosophy/Religious Studies, 1964; 168887 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Owen, Guillermo - Mathematical Sciences, 1969-1978; 168888 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Owen, Karen Lee G. - Philosophy, 1981; 168889 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Page, Edward - Electrical Engineering, 1973-1975; 168890 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Pagnucci, Mirta - Italian and French, 1978-1983; 168891 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Paine, Jerrold M. - Accounting, 1970; 168892 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Pan, Poh Hsi - Geology, 1976-1977; 168893 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Papantoni-Kazakos, Panayota - Electrical Engineering, 1973-1978; 168894 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Parish, John Edward - English, 1947-1980; 168895 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Parks, Alton Zang, Jr. - Architecture, 1970-1978; 168896 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Parramore, Mary L. - NSF Intergovernmental Personnel Act Mobility Program, 1976-1977; 168897 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Paslay, Paul Robert - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1959-1965, 1979-1984; 168898 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Pate, MAJ Hugh P. - Naval Science, 1972-1973; 168899 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Patterson, David S. - History, 1971-1976; 168900 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Patterson, Ronald G. - Shepherd School of Music, 1974-1980; 168901 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Paul, Eric Barlow - Physics, 1964-1966; 168902 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Paulson, Ronald Howard - English, 1963-1967; 168903 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Paulson, Ross E. - History, 1967-1968; 168904 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Paz, Israel M. - Electrical Engineering, 1974-1975; 168905 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Peacocke, Christopher A. - Philosophy, 1984; 168906 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Peasnell, Kenneth Vincent - Accounting (appointment cancelled), 1984; 168907 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Peeler, CAPT Thomas G. - Naval Science, 1979-1983 [?]; 168908 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Peled, Nina - Chemistry, 1977-1978; 168909 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Perkin, Harold - History, 1984; 168910 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Perrine, Richard - Architecture, 1972-1982; 168911 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Person, Henry - Jones School of Administration, 1979-1980; 168912 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Person, Jo A. - Comptroller, 1968-1976 [?]; 168913 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Peters, LTJG Wayne D. - Naval Science, 1979-1981; 168914 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Peterson, Dolores M. - Biomedical Engineering Laboratory, 1979-1983; 168915 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Peterson, William E. - Director of Athletics and Head Football Coach, 1970-1971; 168916 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Pfeffer, Gerald S. - Architecture, 1971-1972; 168917 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Pfeiffer, Wolfgang - Mechanical Engineering, 1964-1965; 168918 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Phelps, Barton - Architecture, 1977-1978; 168919 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Pickar, Gertrude H. - German, 1961-1964; 168920 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Pickard, John Benedict - English, 1956-1963; 168921 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Pickett, Lloyd - Biology, 1962-1964; 168922 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Picologlou, Basil F. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1974-1979; 168923 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Pieper, Howard - Architecture, 1979-1980; 168924 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Pinkerton, MAJ Billy B. - Military Science, 1973-1976; 168925 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Pirsch, John Gregor - Biology, 1963-1964; 168926 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Pitman, H. Russell - Chief Accountant/Assistant to the President/Manager of Campus Business Affairs, 1960-1980; 168927 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Plapp, John E. - Mechanical Engineering, 1956-1968; 168928 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Pomery, John Geoffrey - Ecomonics, 1974-1979; 168929 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Pool, Robert E. - Mathematics, 1981-1982; 168930 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Pop, Julian J. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1980, 1982-1984; 168931 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Poppelbaum, Christian H. - Physics, 1964-1965; 168932 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Porter, Carolyn Jane - English, 1980; 168933 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Potter, CAPT Edward H., Jr. - Department Chairman of Naval Science, 1966-1972; 168934 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Powell, Benjamin N. - Geology, 1970-1980; 168935 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Power, Thomas C. - Psychology, 1983; 168936 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Preston, John F. - Architecture, 1979-1982; 168937 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Preston, Kay - Jones School of Administration, 1980-1981; 168938 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Provencher, Ronald - Anthropology, 1969-1974; 168939 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Pucci, Carlo - Mathematics, 1961; 168940 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Purdy, Edward George - Geology, 1959-1965; 168941 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Queen, LT Robert A. - Naval Science, 1965-1967; 168942 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Quinton, John D. - Commerce, 1967-1968; 168943 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Rachford, Henry H., Jr. - Mathematics, 1964-1982; 168944 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Rahe, Maurice - Mathematics, 1981-1982; 168945 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Ramberg, Ivan B. - Geology, 1982-1983; 168946 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Ramer, Samuel Carroll - History, 1982-1983; 168947 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Randolph, Richard Rannells - Anthropology, 1963-1964; 168948 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Ransom, Harry S., Jr. - Architecture, 1956-1981; 168949 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Rao, Gururaj S. - Electrical Engineering, 1975-1978; 168950 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Rathjen, Diana Pickett - Psychology, 1972-1984; 168951 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Rau, Carl - Physics (1 of 2), 1983-2013; 168952 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Rau, Carl - Physics (2 of 2), 1983-2013; 168953 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Raucher, Alan - History, 1965-1966; 169261 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Rawlinson, Mary C. - Philosophy, 1977-1979; 169262 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Rea, Ronald B. - Architecture, 1974-1978; 169263 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Read, Clark Phares - Biology, 1954-1973; 169264 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Reasoner, David L. - Space Science, 1969-1975; 169265 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Rector, David Lee - Mathematics, 1968-1974; 169266 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Red, William S., III - Manager of the Campus Store/Director of the RMC, 1963-1974 [?]; 169267 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Reed, Kennard W., Jr. - Mathematics, 1965-1966; 169268 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Reedy, Elizabeth K. - English, 1964-1967; 169269 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Reid, Edward B. - Chemistry, 1973-1974; 169270 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Remington, Richard D. - Mathematical Sciences, 1972-1974; 169271 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Resnikoff, Howard L. - Mathematics, 1966-1975; 169272 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Reso, Anthony - Geology, 1980; 169273 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Rhodes, Harold R. - Director of Safety and Security, 1966-1989; 169274 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Rice, Homer C. - Athletic Director and Head Football Coach, 1976-1977; 169275 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Richter, George Holmes - Chemistry/Dean of Graduate Students, 1926-1974; 169276 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Ricouer, Paul - Rockwell Lecturer, 1962-1963; 169277 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Ride, Sally Kristen - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1979-1981; 169278 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Reeves, Norfleet Williamson, Jr. - Jones School of Administration, 1983-1984; 169279 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Robbins, Janet Jo - Health and Physical Education, 1969-1972; 169280 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Robinson, Hoke - Philosophy, 1979-1981; 169281 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Robinson, John Allen - Computer Science/Philosophy (image), 1961-1967; 169282 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Rogers, John J. W. - Geology, 1954-1978; 169283 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Rogerson, Kenneth - Philosophy, 1982-1984; 169284 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Roney, Lois - English, 1980-1982; 169285 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Roos, Keith L. - Germanics, 1967-1968; 169286 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Rose, Jasper Allison - Fine Arts, 1963-1964; 169287 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Rosenberg, Michael - Shepherd School of Music, 1977-1981; 169288 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Rosenberg, T.J. - Space Science, 1966-1968; 169289 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Rosenthal, Haskell Paul - Mathematics, 1972; 169290 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Ross, Allan A. - Shepherd School of Music, 1979-1980; 169291 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Rossini, Frederick D. - Chemistry, 1971-1978; 169292 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Roth, Bertram - Band Director, 1967-1980; 169293 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Rougé, Robert - English, 1977; 169294 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Rowland, Richards A. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1979; 169295 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Roy, Gerald - Physics (appointment terminated), 1964-1965; 169296 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Rudee, Mervyn L. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1964-1974; 169297 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Ruffin, Roy J. - Economics, 1979; 169298 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Rulfs, Mildred L. - Commerce, 1971-1974; 169299 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Rundel, Robert D. - Physics/Space Physics and Astronomy, 1969-1980; 169300 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Rusk, Sigsby Keefer - Electrical Engineering, 1970-1975; 169301 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Ryan, Frank B. - Mathematics, 1966; 169302 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Ryan, Lawrence John - Germanics, 1966-1967; 169303 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Sadler, Mitchell O. - Personnel Administrator, 1967-1981 [?]; 169304 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Saffer, Arnold E. - Economics, 1962-1964; 169305 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Salama, Kamel - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1973-1976; 169306 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Salamy, Joseph G. - Psychology, 1978-1979; 169307 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Salani, Harold J. - Civil Engineering, 1959-1965; 169308 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Saltzberg, Bernard - Electrical Engineering/Biomedical Engineering, 1977-1981; 169309 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Samohyl, Robert W. - Economics, 1970-1975; 169310 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Sandall, Frederick Roger - Fine Arts, 1972; 169311 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Sanders, John Harry - Education, 1960-1963; 169312 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - De Santis, A. A., Jr. - Naval Science, 1978 [?]; 169313 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Santos, Adele de Souza - Architecture, 1973-1979; 169314 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Santos, Antonio Paulo de Souza - Architecture, 1973-1981; 169315 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Sartoris, Nelson - Chemistry, 1981-1982; 169316 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Savage, Catherine - French, 1960-1962; 169317 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Scanlan, Robert H. - Civil Engineering, 1978; 169318 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Schacht, Robert M. - Anthropology, 1978-1980; 169319 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Schearer, Laird D. - Physics, 1965; 169320 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Schmalz, Thomas G. - Chemistry, 1979-1980; 169321 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Schneidau, Herbert - English, 1978; 169322 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Schorre, Charles - Architecture, 1960-1973; 169323 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Schubert, Manfred - Germanics, 1965-1971; 169324 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Schuberth, Richard E. - Psychology, 1977-1981; 169325 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Schussler, Hans Wilhelm - Electrical Engineering, 1984; 169326 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Schutz, Gunther - German, 1961-1962; 169327 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Schwartz, Arnold - Biochemistry/Chemistry, 1971-1976; 169328 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Sclafani, Richard - Philosophy, 1969; 169329 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Sconiers, William Lloyd - Accounting, 1966; 169330 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Scott, John Frederick - Art and Art History, 1977-1981; 169331 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Scott, Robert B. - Geology, 1964-1965; 169332 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Scott, Winton Forrest, Jr. - Architecture, 1970-1973; 169333 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Scoular, David N. - Architecture, 1974-1982; 169334 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Seagrave, Charles E. - Economics, 1967-1972; 169335 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Sebastiani, Michel A. - Health and Physical Education, 1982; 169336 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Segal, Earl - Biology, 1960-1963; 169337 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Sehested, John - Commerce, 1967-1968; 169338 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Seibert, Guy B., Jr. - Mathematical Sciences, 1971-1974; 169339 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Seim, CAPT Richard R. - History, 1979-1980; 169340 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Sethi, Suresh P. - Economics, 1972-1973; 169341 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Setser, George G. - Physics, 1974-1975; 169342 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Severs, Richard K. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1974-1978; 169343 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Shah, Pradeep L. - Electrical Engineering, 1972-1973; 169344 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Sharper, Sue Z. - Religious Studies, 1975-1981; 169345 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Shapiro, Eudice - Shepherd School of Music, 1977-1981; 169346 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Sharpe, Carl Paul - Architecture, 1973-1980; 169347 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Shaw, Peter - Space Science, 1965-1966; 169348 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Shelton, MAJ Hal T. - Military Science, 1969 - [?]; 169349 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Shimada, Toshiyuki - Shepherd School of Music, 1982-1983; 169350 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - Shoemaker, Eugene - Space Science and Geology, 1963-1964; 169351 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - Shreffler, Edwin Hughes - Romance Languages, 1954-1964; 169352 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - Skarginsky, George P. - Russian, 1961-1967; 169353 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Siddall, John B. - Chemistry, 1977; 169354 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Silberschlag, Eisig - Religious Studies, 1983-1984; 169355 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Silvers, Abraham - Mathematical Sciences, 1981-1982; 169356 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Simmons, John E., Jr. - Biology, 1963-1965; 169368 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Simon, William - Sociology, 1977-1979; 169370 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Simpson, Camille E. - Education, 1977; 169372 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Sinder, Philip N. - Shepherd School of Music, 1981-1982; 169373 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Singh, Sadanand - Psychology, 1980-1981; 169375 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Siracusa, Joseph - Spanish and Italian, 1962-1965; 169377 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Siu, Albert K. Q. - Chemistry, 1973-1974; 169381 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Sloan, Jon R. - Geology, 1981; 169382 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Smith, CAPT Edgar L. - Military Science, 1974-[?]; 169383 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Edward T. - Athletic Medical Program, 1962-1977; 169384 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Smith, Gary N. - Economics, 1978-1981; 169385 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Justin - Mathematics, 1976-1978; 169386 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Smith, Michael - Philosophy, 1981-1983; 169387 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Smith, Peggy B. - Psychology, 1971-1973; 169388 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Richard N. - Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering and Materials Science, 1974-1977; 169389 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Snell, David Allen - Economics, 1965; 169390 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Sobel, Margaret F. - French, 1970-1976; 169391 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Somes, LTJG T. E., USN - Naval Science, 1962-[?]; 169392 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Sondow, Jonathan D. - Mathematics, 1977-1978; 169393 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Sorensen, James C. - Jones School of Administration, 1982; 169394 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Sorgee, LT Vernon - Military Science, 1968-[]; 169395 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Sosinsky, Barrie A. - Chemistry, 1978-1982; 169396 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Soudek, Ernst - Germanics, 1969-1972; 169397 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Sparks, CAPT Gene D. - Military Science, 1971-[?]; 169398 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Spence, Dale William - Health and Physical Education, 1963-2003; 169399 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Sperling, Harry S. - Mathematical Sciences, 1973-1980; 169400 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Spitz, Barry - Jones School of Administration, 1978-1979; 169401 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Squire, Charles Francis - Physics, 1947-1960; 169402 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Srinivasan, R. - Electrical Engineering, 1974-1975; 169403 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Staats, William F. - Commerce, 1963-1965; 169404 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Stanford, Geoffrey Brian - Architecture, 1973-1974; 169405 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Stanton, Robert J. - Mathematics, 1974-1981; 169406 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Starnes, LCDR Phillip V. - Naval Science (photograph), 1972-1973; 169407 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Starnes, William P. - Economics, 1978-1980; 169408 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Starr, Mark - Philosophy, 1980-1981; 169409 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Steele, Henry B. - Economics, 1957-1966; 169410 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Steele, CAPT Thomas W. - Naval Science, 1973-1976; 169411 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Steiger, CAPT Michael S. - Military Science, 1971-[?]; 169412 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Steihaug, Trond - Mathematical Sciences, 1981-1983; 169414 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Stein, Arnold - English, n.d.; 169415 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Stelson, Paul Hugh - Physics, 1962-1963; 169416 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Stenzel, Henryk Bronislaw - Geology, 1965-1967; 169417 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Stevens, Paul Michael - Bioengineering/Electrical Engineering, 1972-1980; 169418 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Stevens, Robert V. - Chemistry, 1966-1976; 169419 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Stewart, David - Philosophy, 1964-1965; 169420 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Stewart, George Louis - Biology, 1975-1976; 169421 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Stewart, John F. - Economics, 1981-1983; 169422 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Stinnett, Wayne D., Jr. - Accounting, 1976-1978; 169423 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Stone, Tabor R. - Architecture, 1973-1975; 169424 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Straka, Gerald Milton - History, 1963-1966; 169425 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Stramler, James H., Jr. - Psychology, 1981-1982; 169426 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Streltsova-Adams, Tatiana D. - Geology, 1978-1981; 169427 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Strong, Robert Donald - Director of Chapel Music/Religious Studies, 1969-1976; 169428 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Summers, Edward L. - Accounting, 1965-1967; 169429 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Super, Robert H. - English, 1965-1966; 169430 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Swan, Peter - Physics, 1963-1964; 169431 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Swidler, Steven - Economics, 1979-1980; 169432 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Talbot, Raymond J., Jr. - Space Science, 1971-1981; 169445 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Taniguchi, Alan Y. - Architecture, 1972-1982; 169447 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Tapley, Charles R. - Architecture, 1975-1983; 169448 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Tarrance, Lance, Jr. - Political Science, 1979-1982; 169449 (Box 10, Folder 61)